lcg.com 2016-11-25

# Data Protection and Privacy Policy

                                                                                                   1
 Data Protection and Privacy Policy
 Data Protection Act
 London Capital Group Limited (LCG) may process information relating to you (including
 personal data as defined under the Data Protection Act 1998), including holding such
 information in a manual format or electronic database, in order to satisfy any contractual,
 regulatory or statutory requirements we may have. Unless we receive specific written
 instructions to the contrary, by providing this information you agree that we may process this
 information in order to fulfil such obligations.
 Privacy Policy
 Introduction:
 Protecting the security and privacy of your personal information is important to LCG and to
 the way it conducts its business in compliance with laws on privacy, data protection and data
 security. The purpose of this policy is to outline what information LCG may collect, how it
 uses and safeguards that information and with whom it may share it.
 At LCG, we are committed to maintaining the highest standards of integrity in our business.
 In the course of our business, it is necessary to collect Personal Information about our
 potential clients. We take this activity seriously and seek to provide fair, secure and
 appropriate methods for the handling of Personal Information. All such activities are intended
 to be consistent with both generally accepted privacy ethics and standard business
 practices. Your Personal Information may be shared with a limited number of trusted
 partners and/or affiliates of LCG where such use is restricted to the management of your
 account and will not breach any elements of the UK Data Protection Act 1998.
 If you have any questions or comments about LCG’s Privacy Policy, please contact our
 Customer Support team via the details on the Contacts page.
 Personally Identifiable Information
 Through its websites, LCG will not collect any personally identifiable information about you
 (e.g. your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address ("Personal Information")),
 unless you voluntarily choose to provide it (e.g. by registration, email enquiry, survey). If you
 do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it.
 By submitting your Personal Information you consent to LCG using your Personal
 Information in the ways listed below You also consent to LCG transferring your Personal
 Information outside the European Economic Area where it is necessary for LCG to fulfil its
 contractual, regulatory and legal obligations. We will only transfer Personal Information to
 organisations outside the EEA if we have assessed that the organisation we are sending the
 information to as having appropriate controls and safeguards in place.
 How does LCG use your information?
 LCG may use your information for any one or more of the following purposes:
        to confirm your identity
        to maintain your personal profile
        to manage your account and keep you updated on all matters that concern your
         account
London Capital Group
                                                                          TRADE CONNECTED
1 Knightsbridge, London, SW1X 7LX

                                                                                                2
         to provide the services to you that you have requested including processing
          transactions
         to contact you when necessary or appropriate in relation to the services being
          provided to you
         to provide you with information about our products and services and provide you with
          information or opportunities that we believe might be relevant to you
         to tailor the website or other service we provide to you to your needs and interests
         to create anonymised statistical data
 If you choose not to have your Personal Information used to support LCG’s customer
 relationship programmes (especially direct-marketing or market-research), LCG will respect
 your choice. LCG does not now (and does not intend to in the future) sell, rent or otherwise
 market your Personal Information to third parties.
 You may opt out of receiving marketing emails at any time by selecting the 'unsubscribe' link
 at the top of the emails or by emailing our Customer Support team (via the details on the
 Contacts page) with your request.
 Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically
 When you access its websites, LCG may automatically (i.e. not by registration) collect
 statistical information that is not personally identifiable (e.g. type of Internet browser and
 computer operating system used; domain name of the website from which you came;
 number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed). LCG may use this information and
 share it within the LCG group to measure the use of its website and improve its content.
 Who may LCG disclose Personal Information to?
 Your Personal Information may be disclosed to:
       the Financial Conduct Authority and other regulatory and government bodies whom
          LCG is required to disclose by law;
       financial institutions and other similar organisations that LCG deals with in the course
          of its business;
       service providers and specialist advisers that provide services to LCG;
       any third parties where this is necessary to process a transaction or provide services
          which you have requested;
       introducing brokers or similar brokers who have been contracted to provide us with
          administrative, financial, insurance, research or other services;
       credit providers, courts, tribunals and regulatory authorities as agreed or authorised
          by law;
       credit reporting or reference agencies;
       anyone authorised by you (such as your financial adviser, broker, solicitor or
          accountant).
 Please note LCG will never sell or provide your Personal Information to third parties for
 marketing purposes.
 Generally we require any third party service provider that we share Personal Information
 with, undertake to respect any individual’s right to privacy and comply with the Data
 Protection Principles. These third party service providers may keep a record of any searches
 performed on our behalf and may use the search details to assist other companies in
 performing their searches. Third parties are not covered by this privacy policy.
London Capital Group
                                                                              TRADE CONNECTED
1 Knightsbridge, London, SW1X 7LX

                                                                                                 3
 Third Party Sites
 The LCG web site contains links to other web sites. Please be notified that LCG cannot be
 held responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage all visitors to be
 aware and read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally
 identifiable information.
 Retention of records
 We will keep Personal Information only as long as it is necessary, including for the purposes
 of updating the product or services or as required by law. When the Personal Information is
 no longer required, it will be destroyed either by shredding or other approved destruction
 methods to prevent unauthorised parties from gaining access to the information during and
 after the process. We will safeguard information in our custody.
 Security
 LCG takes precautions to ensure the security of your personal information and strives to
 keep it accurate. LCG carefully protects your personal information from loss, destruction,
 falsification, manipulation, and unauthorised access or unauthorised disclosure and has
 developed and will maintain security procedures to safeguard Personal Information against
 loss, theft, copying, and unauthorised disclosure, use or modification. Access to Personal
 Information is restricted to employees and authorised service providers who need it to
 perform their work.
 Access to your Personal Information held by us
 Under the UK Data Protection Act, you have the right to obtain a copy of any Personal
 Information which we hold about you and to advise us of any perceived inaccuracy (subject
 to certain exceptions).
 If you wish to make an access request, please contact us verifying your identity and
 specifying what information you require. We may charge a fee to cover the cost of verifying
 the application and locating and retrieving, reviewing and copying any material requested.
 Cookies
 Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser
 whilst the user is browsing that website.
 How we use Cookies on our Site and what Information we collect.
 Like most websites, LCG uses cookies to improve your experience on our websites as the
 data from cookies enables us to determine the type of browser and settings you are using,
 where you have been on our website, when you return to the website, where you came from
 and to ensure your information is secure.. We do not link the information we store in cookies
 to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If you choose to opt
 out of cookies you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas will be limited.
 We would strongly recommend that you allow cookies on our website to ensure you have the
 best possible experience. Turning off cookies may result in reduced performance of our
 website and trading platform, however if you would still like to opt out of cookies, you can do
London Capital Group
                                                                          TRADE CONNECTED
1 Knightsbridge, London, SW1X 7LX

                                                                                                  4
 this through your website browser. Our customer support team would be happy to talk you
 through this process if you require assistance.
 For more information about the types of cookies LCG uses please see our Cookie policy.
 Use of Web Beacons
 Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes
 known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web
 beacons collect only limited information which includes a cookie number, time and date of a
 page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. We may also
 carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any
 personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular
 campaign.
 Privacy Statement Changes
 LCG may change this privacy statement at any time. You are advised to read this statement
 each and every time you access the site so that you are satisfied with the privacy conditions
 under which you provide LCG with your personal information.
 October 2015
London Capital Group
                                                                         TRADE CONNECTED
1 Knightsbridge, London, SW1X 7LX
